你看过我们的银行对帐单了吗
Have you seen our bank statement?
不会出错了吧
Can this be right?
就是嘛  天啊
I know. God,
除了我小时候  双层夹心饼上市那会
I haven't seen my savings take a hit like this...
我的存款就没这么少过
since I was a kid and they came up with Double Stuf Oreos.
我们的存款哪去了呢
What happened to all of our money?
我不清楚他们做了什么
I'm not sure exactly what they did...
但是我倾向于责怪安然公司倒闭案
but I'm inclined to blame Enron.
大概因为你在做实习工
I guess with you doing the internship,
所以我们有些入不敷出
we're spending more than we're bringing in.
是啊  或许我应该辞掉
Yeah, maybe I should quit
找个有薪水的工作
and get a job that pays.
可你总算找到你喜欢的工作了
But you're finally doing something that you love.
我不能要求你放弃的
I mean, I can't ask you to give that up.
不过你喜欢做的工作是挖金子
Although it would be nice if the thing that you loved
那就好了
was finding gold.
我觉得我们太小题大作了
You know, I think we're making too big a deal out of this.
我们这个月迟些付账单
We'll pay our bills late this month.
下个月我们就节省一些开销
Next month we'll cut back on a few things.
而且或许我们可以变换一下
And maybe we start eating out of Joey's refrigerator
到乔伊家的冰箱找食物
for a change.
你是大厨
You're a chef.
用苏打粉跟啤酒你会做什么菜
What can you make out of baking soda and beer?
最糟糕的情况下
Worst-case scenario is,
我们只好找我父母借钱
we borrow some money from my parents.
不可以  而且我们也不借钱
No, and we're not borrowing money.
-为什么   -我们是宾家人
- Why not? -We don't do that.
宾家人从不跟人借钱
We are Bings.
我爸唯一教会我的事  就是
If there's one thing my father taught me, it was...
去别人家泳池之前
well, to always knock
一定要先敲门
before going into the pool house.
还有  永远都不要向人借钱
The other thing is, never borrow money.
我不知道你这么有自尊
I had no idea you had this much pride.
没错  我有  我是你男人
That's right, I do. I am your man.
我会让我们度过难关的
I'm gonna get us through this situation...
就算你要加倍努力地工作
even if it means you working twice as hard.
《老友记》  第九季 第16集  隆胸记
Friends S09E16 The One With The Boob Job
-我要回去了  -为什么
- I'm gonna go.  - Why?
我有好几天没有回家了
I haven't been home in days,
而且我需要多拿几件衣服
and I need to get more clothes.
你不用回去
You don't have to go.
我有衣服可以给你穿
I have something that'll fit you.
我穿女生的紧身衣  是在逗你
I put that tube top on as a joke.
我想要你留下来
I want you to stay.
我也想要留下来
I want to stay too.
但是这几条内裤我都穿遍了
But I've got as much use out of these boxers as I can.
-要不反过来再穿呢  -已经反过了
- Why don't you turn them inside  - Done it.
我几个小时之后就回来
I'll be back in a couple of hours.
好吧  我会想你的
All right. I'll miss you.
我也是
Me too.
你知道吗  我刚惊觉到一件事
You know what? I just realized something.
我不想回家
I don't want to go home.
太好了  好的  我去拿紧身衣
Great! Okay, I'll go get the tube top.
不  我的意思是
No, no, what I mean is...
我不喜欢回去自己的公寓里
I hate going back to my apartment now.
一方面是因为  我住的房间又小又乱
Partly because I live above a known crack den...
但是  主要是因为
...but, you know, mostly because when I'm there,
我回去的时候  真的好想你
I really miss you.
所以...
So...
我们同居好不好
do you want to move in together?
哇  迈克·汉尼根
Wow, Mike Hanigan...
你倒真有两把刷子  让女生说"好耶"
...you sure know how to make a girl say ''Hell, yeah.''
那我们要这样做吗
So we're doing it?
好啊  就这样  让我们住在一起
Yeah, let's do it. Let's live together.
我们真的要同居了吗
We're really gonna move in together?
是啊
Yeah.
我一直都想要跟男生同居
I've always wanted to live with a guy.
袜子捡起来
Pick up your socks.
把马桶圈给我放下来
Put down the toilet seat.
不  我再也不能再做爱了
No, we are not having sex anymore.
一定会很好玩
It's gonna be fun.
-嘿  乔伊  -嘿
- Hey, Joey.  - Hey.
听着  我要你跟我保证
Listen, I need to know that what
一会我要拜托你的事情
I'm about to ask you...
你永远都不会告诉钱德勒
will never get back to Chandler.
如果说我  没有想过那件事
I'd be lying if I said I hadn't
那是骗你的
thought about it myself.
但是钱德勒是我最好的朋友
But Chandler is my best friend.
那是不对的
It would be wrong.
感觉应该不错  却是不对的
Good, but wrong.
好的  首先  感觉会是棒翻天
Okay, first of all, it would be great.
但那不是我说的事  我要跟你借钱
But that's not what I'm here to talk to you about. I need to borrow money.
哦  不好说  莫妮卡  你知道
Oh, I don't know, Monica. You know
借钱给朋友不是什么好事
lending friends money is always a mistake.
但是钱德勒借过你钱啊
But Chandler lent you money.
而他也会告诉你  那不是什么好事
And he would tell you it was a mistake.
别这样  我只是...
Come on, I just....
需要付房租跟一些帐单
I need it for some rent and some other bills.
多少钱呢
Well, how much?
两千块
Two thousand dollars?
你以为我是谁  肥皂剧明星吗
What do you think I am, a soap opera star?
-是啊  -没错  我就是
- Yeah.  - That's right, I am.
-嗨  你们好  -嘿
- Hi, you guys.  - Hey.
袋子里是什么
What's in the bag?
艾玛已经开始会爬了
You know how Emma started crawling?
我觉得这个地方  对婴儿很不安全
I realized that this place is very unsafe for a baby...
所以我去店里买了些东西
...so I went to the store
可以保护婴儿在公寓里活动
and I got some stuff to baby-proof the apartment.
哦  天啊  保护婴儿
Oh, God, baby-proofing.
有什么了不起的
Why is it such a big deal now?
我小的时候  经常发生
You know, when I was a kid, it was like:
"哎呀  乔伊跌下楼梯了"
''Whoops, Joey fell down the stairs.''
或者  "糟糕  乔伊又电到自己了"
Or, ''Whoops, Joey electrocuted himself again.''
你要找人帮忙装这些东西吗
Anyway, are you going to get a handyman to install this stuff?
不  我自己来就行了
No, I was just gonna do it myself.
-你要自己来  -是啊  不行吗
- You're gonna do it?  - Yeah. Why?
你觉得女人做不来吗
You don't think a woman can do this?
女人可以  你不行
Women can. You can't.
莫妮卡  请你告诉乔伊  他是猪
Monica, will you please tell Joey that he is a pig.
你是猪  而你做不来
You're a pig. And you can't do this.
什么
What?
别这样  我自己都找到五金店了
What? Come on, I found the hardware store all by myself.
五金店不就在街角嘛
The store's right down the street.
街角就有五金店啊
There is a hardware store right down the street?
嘿  各位  我们有好消息要宣布
Hey, you guys? Okay, we've got great news.
菲比跟我要搬到一起了
Phoebe and I are moving in together.
恭喜
Congratulations.
好兴奋  我从来都没跟男生同居过
I know, it's so exciting. You know, I've never lived with a guy before.
其实跟女生同居是一样的
Well, it's just like living with a girl,
只是他们不会偷用你的化妆品
only they don't steal your makeup.
除非他们扮演
Unless they're playing
"我要有妹妹  她长什么样"
''This Is What My Sister Would Look Like.''
我妹长得不是很可爱
Yeah, she's not so cute.
我去洗手间
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
上完把马桶坐垫放下来
Well, you put down the toilet seat.
是的  亲爱的
Yes, dear.
那是你们在玩的游戏吗
Is that a bit you guys do?
是啊  我们在模仿你们俩个
Uh-huh. We're playing you two.
我们才没有那样
We don't do that.
告诉她  我们没有
Tell her we don't do that.
是的  亲爱的
Yes, dear.
不敢相信你们要同居了
I can't believe you're moving in together.
真替你们高兴
I'm happy for you guys.
我听到婚礼进行曲了
I hear wedding bells.
莫妮卡  别急好吗
Monica, slow down, okay?
我只是很兴奋要跟他同居了而已
I'm just excited to be living with him.
你知道的  我是说  我不知道...
You know, I mean, I don't know...
我能预见  有天跟迈克结婚吗
...can I see someday being married to Mike?
是的  当然
Sure. Yeah.
我可以想像
I could picture myself
穿着婚纱走在红毯上
walking down the aisle in a wedding dress...
婚纱主要突显我的胸部
.that highlights my breasts
但是是很高雅的爆乳
in an obvious yet classy way.
但问我想不想要
But do I want
在康乃狄克州的好学区附近
that house in Connecticut near
有所房子...
the good schools...
迈克可以和我
...where Mike and I could
送我们的小苏菲  跟小迈克去上学
send little Sophie and Mike Jr.?
哦  我的天  我愿意
Oh, my God, I do.
我不晓得你是这么传统的人
I had no idea you were so conventional.
我也没想到  大概我是的
I know. I guess I am.
我的天  开着沃尔沃
Oh, my God, load up the Volvo,
我就是中产阶级妇女了
I want to be a soccer mom.
你准备好要走了吗
You ready to go?
当然好了  新室友
Yeah, you bet, roomie.
你是说"新郎"吧
Don't you mean ''groomie''?
-你们在说什么  -拜托
- What are you talking about?  - Please.
这些家伙  我们都还没一起住
These guys. We haven't even moved in yet,
他们就要我们选结婚用的瓷器了
and they have us picking out china patterns.
结婚用的瓷器
China patterns!
很容易嘛  还说"你不行..."
This is easy. ''Can't do this....''
哇  还真的咧  就是不行
Wow, seriously. Can't do this.
-嘿  乔伊  -嘿
- Hey, Joe.  - Hey.
听着  我需要你帮个忙
Look, I need to ask you a favor,
而且不能跟莫妮卡说
and we can't tell Monica anything about it.
我以为你们之间没有秘密
I thought you guys didn't have secrets.
官方说法上是那样没错
That will remain the official party line.
莫妮卡跟我  有一点点经济上的问题
Look, Monica and I are having a little financial trouble.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
什么  你怎么知道的
What? How do you know?
我猜的  你知道的
I just figured it out, you know?
你没有工作  而且现在经济又很萧条
I mean, you're not working, and the economy is bad.
哦  对
Oh, right.
这是我反应最快的一次了
That is the fastest I have ever thought.
反正...
Anyway...
我需要跟你借点钱
I need to borrow some money.
当然可以  多少钱  两千块吗
Oh, sure. Yeah, how much? Two thousand dollars?
是的  正是两千块
Yes, $2000 exactly.
你是怎么知道的
How did you know that?
我知道你之前赚多少钱
I know how much you used to make,
而且我也知道你们的房租
and I know how much your rent is.
哦  好的
Oh, okay.
我真是天才
I am on fire.
听着  你真好
Listen, this is really nice.
你是不是开了一张
Did you write a check
两千块的支票给莫妮卡
to Monica for $2000?
莫妮卡跟你借钱了
Did Monica borrow money from you?
好像是
Kind of.
我不敢相信她竟然这样做
I can't believe her.
她跟你说我们经济出问题了吗
Did she tell you we were having money problems?
不  不是为了你们的经济问题
No, no, no. It wasn't because of your money problems.
是她自己的东西
It was for something for her.
什么
What?
很私人的东西
Something personal.
她要买两千块的东西
What would she get for $2000
还不能告诉我
that she wouldn't tell me about?
打扰一下
Excuse me.
隆乳手术
Boob job.
隆乳手术  她根本不需要啊
A boob job? She doesn't need that.
太疯狂了
That's crazy.
不算太疯狂  好吗
Well, it's not that crazy, okay?
把咪咪变小才叫做疯狂
Making them smaller, that would be crazy.
嘿  我想要问你
Oh, hey, I wanted to ask you about
关于莫妮卡"新郎"的玩笑
Monica's little ''groomie'' joke.
我想大家会笑
Well, I think the reason people laughed is
是因为"新室友"和"新郎"音近
that it's a play on the word ''roomie.''
我听得懂这个笑话  真是高深啊
I get the joke. Sophisticated as it was.
不  我要说的是...
No, the thing I want to say is....
或许我们之前就应该先谈过
Maybe we should've talked about this before.
我们同居之后
Us living together,
你没有期望我会求婚吧
you're not expecting a proposal, right?
-哦  不  一点也没有  -好的
- Oh, no, no. Not at all.  - Okay.
我们才刚搬进来一起住
We're just moving in right now.
将来怎样顺其自然
We'll see where it goes.
对  这就是个问题
Yeah, well, that's the thing.
对我而言  这已经是我的极限了
For me, it's as far as it can ever go.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
听着  菲比  我...
Look, Phoebe, I....
我非常爱你  但我不想再结婚了
I love you very much. But I never want to get married again.
只是我的第一次婚姻太...
It's just, my first marriage was...
太糟糕了  我已经对婚姻失去信心了
you know, such a disaster that I kind of lost faith in the whole idea.
有那么糟吗
Was it that bad?
到最后...有一次
At one point, near the end...
她故意便便在我的...
she deliberately defecated on my
哦  那真糟
Okay, well, that's bad. Yeah.
但你不认为
But don't you think it might be different
换个人会不一样吗
with someone else? Perhaps...
或许是一个
a blond
会在厕所便便的金发女郎
who always uses the toilet?
除了便在海里的那次
Except for once in the ocean.
听着  不是结婚对象是谁的问题
Look, it's not about who I would marry.
我第一次结婚的时候
I was certain the first time I got married
我坚信会白头到老  但我错了
it'd last forever. I was wrong.
但是  只是
But, it just
菲比  问题不在你
Look, Phoebe, it's not about you.
我只是再也不想结婚了
I just never want to get married again.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你介意吗  如果你介意的话
Are you okay with that? If not,
或许我们同居  不是个好主意
maybe us moving in together isn't the best idea.
可以  哦  我当然不想结婚
No. Oh, I definitely don't want to get married.
我只想确定你也不想结婚
I just wanted to make sure you didn't want to, too.
因为如果我们住在一起了
Because if we move in
你再开始改变主意...
and you start changing your mind...
我们就有麻烦了  先生
...there is gonna be hell to pay, mister.
相信我  我永远不...
Trust me. I will never
好的  我知道了
Yeah, I get that. Yeah.
嗨  最后你决定请人来帮忙了
Hi. So you gave in and decided to call someone?
是啊  不知道我当时在想什么
Yeah. I don't know who I was kidding.
我连筷子都不会用
I can barely use chopsticks.
-都装好了  -非常感谢
- You're all set.  - Oh, thank you so much.
等等  你忘了你的...
Wait. You forgot your...
玩具
...game.
谢谢你
Thank you.
嘿  瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
我身材完美的老婆在这呢
There she is, my perfectly proportioned wife.
别看我  我从来没有听懂过他的笑话
Don't look at me. I never get his jokes.
-谢谢你  -不  不  别谢我
- Thank you?   -No, no. Don't thank me.
谢谢你  你知道吗
Thank you. Do you know
我希望你不要改变任何一点
there is not one thing I would change about you?
一点都不要变  而且特别是...
Not one single thing. And definitely not...
那两点
two single things.
好的  你真的很怪
Okay, you're being weird.
你想上床吗  还是做了什么错事
Do you want sex, or did you do something bad?
不  我就是爱你这模样  我爱你的
No. No. No. I just love the way you look. I am warm
身材
for your form.
传统上  一般都是说 "你很漂亮"
Okay, you know the old classics like, you know, ''You look nice''?
这句话还适用
They're still okay.
但是"你很漂亮"可能只是代表
But ''you look nice'' could mean that I'm saying,
"你的脸蛋看起来漂亮"
''Your face looks nice.''
我想要赞美你的身体
I want to compliment your body.
我是说  我一点都不想它改变
I mean, I wouldn't change it at all.
而且更详细地说  就是
And more specifically,
我不想让任何部位变大
I wouldn't want anything to get any bigger.
-好的  -我是说...
- Okay.  - I mean...
你也不会想要我身体的某部份变大
...you wouldn't want any part of me to get any bigger,
不是吗
would you?
此题不用回答
Don't answer that.
我还以为那老兄不可能更怪了
Just when you thought that dude couldn't get any weirder.
你觉得他  为什么要担心我会变大
Why do you think he was so worried about me getting bigger?
我不知道  这事儿从何而起啊
I don't know. I mean, what brought that on?
我的天  我们正努力要怀孕...
Oh, my God. You know what, we're trying to get pregnant...
所以他可能  很怕我的身材会变形
...so he's probably starting to freak out that my body's gonna change.
你认为是这样吗
You think that's what it is?
你也听到了
You heard him.
"不要变大  你很完美了
''No bigger. You're perfect.
不要再变大了"
Just don't get any bigger.''
天啊  他听起来就像是
My God, he sounded just like
我高中的摔角教练
my high-school wrestling coach.
我必须要跟钱德勒谈谈
I'm gonna have to talk to Chandler.
是啊  如果你不去  我去
Yeah. If you don't, I will.
你的身材必然会走样
Of course your body's gonna change.
你的胸部会变大
Your breasts are gonna get bigger...
你的屁股会变大
...your ass is gonna get bigger...
你的膀胱会失控
.you're gonna lose bladder control.
我的天  真是奇妙的过程啊
God, it's just such a magical time.
听着  我想向你请教关于婚姻的事
Hi. Listen, I wanted to ask you something about marriage.
太好了  现在你是跑来取笑我吗
Oh, great. Now you're seeking me out to make jokes?
大家在一起的时候被取笑
I mean, I can see
我可以理解
if we're all hanging out,
但是跑到我家来...
but to come to my home....
不  我真的想知道你的意见
No, I really want to know how you feel about it.
为什么
Why?
迈克永远不想要结婚
Mike doesn't ever want to get married.
-永远吗   -永远
- Never? - Never.
哇  你还要跟他同居吗
Wow. Are you still gonna move in with him?
我想啊  但是我要你告诉我
I want to, but I wanted you to tell me
结婚真的没什么大不了
that marriage really isn't that big a deal.
没结婚也不必后悔
You know, that I won't be missing out on anything.
因为婚姻烂毙了
That marriage stinks.
是啊  婚姻烂毙了
Yeah, marriage stinks.
如果你想看到
I mean, if you want to see
男人变肥  女人不再除毛
a man gain weight and a woman stop shaving
就叫他们结婚吧
get them married.
那不是你真正的感觉  对吧
That's not how you really feel, is it?
不是  我很抱歉
No, I'm sorry.
我知道这不是你想听到的话
I know it's not what you want to hear,
但是我没有办法说谎  我喜欢结婚
but I can't help it. I love marriage.
真的吗  你这个"离婚专家"
Seriously, you? ''Divorce-o''?
如果你要帮我取绰号
If you have to call me a name,
我比较喜欢   "罗斯  离婚王"
I'd prefer ''Ross, the Divorcer.''
听起来较酷
It's just cooler.
听着  我知道我的婚姻并不成功
Look, I know my marriages didn't exactly work out...
但我喜欢  两个人可以如此的投入
but, you know, I loved being that committed to another person.
在卡罗尔变成女同性恋之前
And Carol and I had some good times
我们有过许多快乐的时光
before she became a lesbian.
之后还有一次
And once afterward.
反正  很抱歉
Anyway, I'm sorry.
没关系  这是你的真实感受
It's okay. That's how you feel.
但是  别这样  住在一起也很棒阿
But, come on, I mean, living together will be great.
我是说你们会很快乐的
I mean, you guys have so much fun.
而且你爱着迈克
And you love Mike.
我是很爱迈克
I do love Mike.
是啊  不是吗
Yeah, see?
你之前也很期待同居的
And you were so excited about moving in together before...
而且你知道吗  期待是对的
...and you know what, you should be.
这是很大的一步
It's a big deal.
是啊  我想你说的对
Yeah, I guess you're right.
是啊  谢谢  真有帮助  谢谢
Yeah, thanks. This helped. Thanks.
离婚王拯救众生
The Divorcer to the rescue.
-并没有比较酷  -我听到了
- It's not cooler.  - Yeah, I just heard it.
瑞秋
Rach?
Rachel?!
所以我想做什么喜欢的事情都不行吗
So I can't do anything I like?!
嘿  瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
完美  什么都不必改变  完美无缺
Perfection. Wouldn't change a thing. Not a thing.
-亲爱的  -怎样
- Honey?  - Yeah?
关于那件事
About that.
我会变的
I'm going to change.
是的  但是亲爱的  你不需要
Yes, but, honey, you don't have to.
我会变大的
I'm gonna get bigger.
亲爱的  我...
Honey, I....
我喜欢你胸部现在的样子
I love your breasts the way they are.
大男人
Fascist.
我的胸部会变大的
My breasts are gonna get bigger
不管你喜不喜欢
whether you like it or not.
而且不只是我的胸部
And it's not just my breasts.
我的屁股也会变大
My ass is gonna get bigger too.
你的屁股
Your ass?!
而且如果她的手脚也变大  别太惊讶
And don't be surprised if her hands and her feet get bigger too.
-他们也会吗  -这就像整套的一样
- They do that?  - It's kind of a package deal.
天啊  为什么
God, why?
为什么你要对自己做这种事呢
Why would you want to do that to yourself?
我以为这是我们俩都想要的
I thought it was something that we both wanted.
如果这对你那么重要  胸部那块
If it means that much to you,
我或许可以释怀
I may be able to get onboard with the boobs...
但是大屁股还有大脚丫
but the giant ass and the big clown feet?
哦  天啊  钱德勒
Oh, my God, Chandler.
如果你连这个都受不了
If you can't handle this,
那你到了医院要怎么办...
what will you be like in the hospital...
加上流血和尖叫声
...with the blood and screaming
还有那个  从她身体挤出来的小小人
and the little person that's shooting out of her?
什么
What?
乔伊  你为什么要跟钱德勒说
Joey, why did you tell Chandler
莫妮卡要去做隆乳手术呢
that Monica was getting a boob job?
因为她是要啊
Because she is.
钱德勒知道我跟你借钱了
Chandler knows I borrowed the money.
为了要做隆乳手术
For your boob job.
-乔伊  -结束了
- Joe... - It's over.
好了  所以我借出了四千块
Okay, so I'm out $4000
结果没有人的胸部会变大
and nobody's boobs are getting any bigger?
嘿  嘿  你们觉得这样如何呢
Hey. Hey, what do you guys think about this:
罗斯  离婚侠
Ross, the Divorce Force.
-比较好了  -是吗
- Better.  - Yeah?
非常酷
Very cool.
嘿  菲比 我真的很高兴
Hey, Pheebs? You know, I'm really glad
那天你过来找我谈了
you came to talk to me the other day...
希望我有帮上忙
...and I hope I was a little helpful.
是啊  帮助很大
Yeah, you were helpful.
-是啊  很谢谢你  -很好  很好
- Yeah. No, thank you.  - Good. Good.
因为我越想越觉得...
Because the more I thought about it, the more I realized...
婚姻对你而言  不见得是必经之路
...I don't think marriage is necessarily the right path for you.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
我知道那天在咖啡馆的时候...
I know the other day in the coffeehouse...
你很沉醉于当中产阶级妇女什么的
you were all caught up in the whole soccer-mom thing...
但是那是真的你吗
...but is that really you?
你可以想像自己开着沃尔沃吗
I mean, can you honestly picture yourself in a Volvo?
富豪汽车是太有棱有角了
They are awfully boxy.
我是说  婚姻对你而言  是很无趣的
I mean, I don't know, you'd be so bored with marriage.
那太中规中矩了
I mean, it's so normal.
是啊
Yeah.
嘿  需要帮忙吗
Hey, can I help?
我们爬了四层楼
Well, we climbed up four flights of stairs,
好不容易通过狭窄的通道
maneuvered a narrow hallway...
躲过一只狂犬病斗牛狗
dodged a rabid pit bull.
但是最后这三尺路才是最崎岖的
But these last three feet are where it gets really tricky.
有时候你的话真伤人
You know, sometimes your words, they hurt.
嘿  你们要把这个放哪呢
Hey, where do you guys want this?
是啊  快点  因为真的很重
Yeah, seriously, because this is really heavy.
不是我  我只是假装扶着
I mean, not for me, because I'm only
但他们几个真的快被压死了
pretending to hold it, but for these guys.
最后再问你一次结婚的事
Just one last time on the marriage thing.
没有再考虑的空间吗
There's no wiggle room?
一点都没有
None at all?
没有  你也不想结婚  不是吗
No, but you don't want to get married either, right?
没错
Right.
不过  我是真的想要结婚
Except that I do want to get married.
不能在楼下卸货前先谈这个吗
Couldn't have had this conversation down at the truck, huh?
什么  你想要结婚
What? You want to get married?
总有一天
Someday.
得了疝气了...
And...hernia.
我从未有过正常的生活
I haven't had a normal life.
而我也从没有觉得缺失过什么
And I never felt like I was missing out on anything.
但是现在我觉得
But it feels like now it's my turn
该轮到我拥有正常的东西了
to have some of the regular stuff.
你为什么不早说呢
Why didn't you say something before?
我之前不确定我有多想要
I didn't know how much I wanted it.
而且我爱你  我想要跟你一起住
And I love you, and I wanted to live with you.
我也想跟你一起住  我们就搬到一起吧
I want to live with you too. I mean, let's do that.
但是我做不到
But I don't think I can.
当我不清楚未来会怎样时
It was okay to move in
是可以搬到一起
when I didn't know what was gonna happen.
但已经知道是毫无未来了
But I can't move in knowing nothing is
我做不到
ever gonna happen.
我们可以至少先试试同居吧
Can we at least try living together?
你或许会改变对婚姻的想法
You might change your mind about marriage.
你会改变你的想法吗
Are you gonna change yours?
不会
No.
我也不会
Me neither.
我需要一个对未来有共同梦想的人
I think I need to be with someone who wants what I want.
但是我不想要结束
But I don't want this to end.
我也不想要结束
No, I don't want it to end either.
我不敢相信就要这样结束了
I can't believe this is gonna end.
我会把我的东西打包好
I guess I'll have my stuff picked up.
好的
Yeah. Okay.
好的  那么...
Okay, so....
再见
Goodbye.
-再见  迈克  -拜  迈克
- Take it easy, Mike.  - Bye, Mike.
我很遗憾  菲比
I'm so sorry, Pheebs.
我们都很不好受
We're all sorry.
往好处想
Look on the bright side.
至少你可以远离那张丑椅子了
At least you won't have to live with this ugly chair.
这个就是你的  对不对
That was here already, huh?
我爱你
I love you.
我办到了  我办到了
I did it! I did it!
太好了
All right.
最好拿多一点
I'd better take all I can carry.
谁知道下次能不能打得开呢
Who knows when I'll be able to get in here again, huh?